Viewers all over the world, begin to release yourself to the present.
Let go of all unforgiveness.
Let go of all resentment, anger, bad feelings towards anyone, in Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Say, "My heart, let go of all unforgiveness, resentment, anger, bad feelings towards anyone".
In Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, I want to be like Jesus in my heart.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever you have that pain or affliction -
Jesus, Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
The Restorer!
The Healer!
Wherever it is located - that affliction, disease, sickness - wherever it is located in your organs,
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Freedom to your bones!
Freedom to your kidneys!
Freedom to your liver!
Freedom to your blood!
Freedom to your tendons!
Freedom to your organs!
Freedom!
Open your lips and begin to confess your freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, freedom to my bones, liver, kidneys, tendons and womb!
Freedom!
I can hear freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Confess freedom!
Confess freedom and begin to live in your confession!
In the name of Jesus, begin to live in your confession!
I'm living in my confession.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!